https://www.identilam.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Talk to our experts+44 (0)1293 851711FAQsAboutCase studiesDownloadsThe IDentiBlogContact usClient Login
Call us Email usAboutCase studiesDownloadsThe IDentiBlogContact usClient LoginID Card & Badging SoftwareCompicComPicWebConference/ID card creatorBadge & trackRFID cards & badgesBarcode BadgesEvent Media Accreditation and TicketingAPI IntegrationID card & badge printersDoppie 100 printerDoppie 300 printerDoppie 450 printerDoppie retransfer printerPrinter Ribbons and AccessoriesBadging services for corporate ID, conferences & eventsOn-site event & conference badging serviceBadge Typesplastic badgesConference card insertsIDhesive folding badgesFolding paper badgesPop-out plastic insertsReusable name badgesLanyardsScreen Printed LanyardsDye sublimation lanyardsEmbroidered lanyardsPlain from stockSafety lanyardsSlider breakawayLanyard AttachmentsAttachment ClipsAttachment ringsBranded lanyardsBreakaway lanyardsMotorsport Lanyards & Pit Pass HoldersSnap bucklesBadge reels & yo-yosMobile phone attachmentsBottle openers and holdersWhistles, zip lanyards & pen holdersUSB lanyardsCustom lanyards & attachmentsBling lanyardsMobile phone lanyards & pouchesCarabiner lanyardsLuggage strap lanyardsEco lanyardsHow to orderBadge accessoriesName badge holdersClear plastic walletsClear rigid walletsFolding flexible walletsColoured flexible walletsEmbossed walletsWeather resistant walletsOpen rigid card holdersRotating card holdersRigid multi card holdersRigid place settingsClosed rigid card holderConference badge holdersBadge reels & yo-yosPlastic badge reelsMetal badge reelsCarabiner badge reelsBranded/corporate badge reelsPrinter Ribbons and AccessoriesAttachmentsMetal strap clipsSelf Adhesive Badge AttachmentsPlastic strap clipsMagnetic attachmentsStud clipsBall neck chainsID card grippersCarabiner attachment strapsBadge boxes & traysCredential walletsEnamel medals, ribbons & dog tags
Home / IDentilam Privacy policy – GDPRIDentilam has a firm commitment to privacy and security. This statement confirms our commitment and practices for the collection and use of information gathered via our website www.identilam.co.uk and/or other means, e.g. at trade shows.Any personal data collected will be handled according to the 6 principles of Article 5 of GDPR 2016.Information CollectionIn all cases, IDentilam is the sole owner of all information collected on its site and will not sell, trade, share, or lease this information to others in ways different from that disclosed in this statement.Optional enquiry forms may be used on our websites to collect contact information (such as name and email address). This information will be used to deliver the information/services which the user has requested.IDentilam does not collect sensitive data, such as race, religion, or political affiliations via its websites.Use of your personal informationWe will only use any personal information provided by the user via web forms for the purposes for which it is provided, or where allowed by law.On occasion we may send out e-mails or postal mail shots informing users of new feature announcements and news about IDentilam products and services. These e-mails are relevant to the provision of the service/information requested by the user.Press releases and customer testimonials may be posted publicly on IDentilam websites but only after permission has been obtained from the subject/s.Any data collected via our ComPicWeb sites for provision of accreditation and badging services is for the specific purpose agreed in each individual contract and will be used for no other purpose.Opt OutUsers may opt out of receiving future mailings using the tick box on the enquiry form. A no mail option is also available to the user on each email which is sent out or by sending to nomail@identilam.co.uk.Controlling the use of your personal informationInformation is held internally at IDentilam and is confidential. We will hold such information only for the purposes for which it is provided and for as long as necessary and will not pass it to any other parties, unless this is made clear to the user.If a user chooses not to receive promotional emails from IDentilam and advises us of their choice (opt out as above), they are automatically removed from the mailing service and no further emails will be sent.CookiesCookies are tiny text files stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. Please note that cookies can’t harm your computer. We don’t store personally identifiable information in the cookies created, but we do use encrypted information gathered from them to help improve your experience of the site.Our web analytics providers use cookies to define user sessions, as well as to provide a number of key features in analytics reports. Our analytics providers set or update cookies only to collect data required for the reports. Additionally, they use only first-party cookies. This means that all cookies set by them for our domain send data only to the servers for our domain. This effectively makes analytics cookies the personal property of our website domain, and the data cannot be altered or retrieved by any service on another domain.By accessing our corporate website you agree to the use of cookies.If you do not wish for us to use cookies when you visit our website please adjust your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. The Help option on the menu bar of your web browser should explain to you how to do this.Session cookies are used on our ComPicWeb sites to provide user login functionality.You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.orgInformation securityIDentilam takes every precaution to protect users’ information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure in accordance with the GDPR 2016.Access to personal information is given to our employees where necessary in the execution of their duties and all employees who have access to personal data or are associated with the handling of that data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of that data.We believe that all available measures have been taken to prevent unauthorised access to information collected via the website or other means.LinksIDentilam’s corporate websites do not contain links to other non-IDentilam sites. However, our websites may be accessed via links from other third party sites. Please be aware that IDentilam is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and no personal information gathered via the IDentilam site is made available to them.ComPicWeb sites may contain links to the clients own website or other associated site, as agreed and confirmed by both parties in the site/service specification.Third Party SoftwareIDentilam uses 3rd party software from Adobe (Acrobat Reader) on our site. Acrobat Reader is required to view product literature etc which is provided in a PDF format. Each of these companies operate their own privacy and security policies which can be viewed on their website: www.adobe.com/privacy.html.Notification of changesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notification of changes on our websites so users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.Enforcement of this privacy statementIDentilam welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions, please contact The Helpline at IDentilam by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail using the details below.IDentilam Helpline IDentilam John Bostock House Faygate Horsham West Sussex RH12 4DNTel: 01293 851711 Fax: 01293 851742 Email: helpline@identilam.co.ukLike UsFollow usSubscribeConnectRead our BlogKeep Me Updated - Don't Miss A ThingJoin the 1000's of ID Experts and Professionals. Stay up to date with all your ID card, event badging and printing needs.NameCompanyEmail CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
We guarantee 100% privacy. Your information will not be shared.
This site uses cookies: Find out more.Okay, thanks
